[Music] It
[Música]
seems to me
me parece
Well I'm freaking out but I'll tell you one thing
Pues yo flipo yo pero te digo una cosa
talking about this I think we should
hablando de esto yo creo que deberíamos
talk because we know we know we
de contar porque sabemos sabemos
remember the Soraya controversy that I don't
recordamos la polémica de Soraya que no
know if she can I don't know if she deleted it from her
sé si lo puede no sé si lo borró de su
Twitter or not I don't
Twitter o no lo borró Es que no me
remember like Twitter Soraya arnela not
acuerdo como Twitter Soraya arnelas no
for me You can go to hell
por mí Te puedes ir al cuerno
with fire na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
con fuego na na na na na na na na na na
Search search well because
Busca busca bueno porque
Soraya Nela arnela yes I remember the
Soraya Nela arnela sí me acuerdo del
tweet that I saw it in a gossip video I don't
tweet que lo vi en un vídeo de salseo no
know if I don't know if
sé si no sé si seguirá
the tweet is still public it's that I remember
el tweet público es que me acuerdo
because I looked for it when you were at the
porque lo busqué cuando estabas tú en lo
other day at the event because
del otro día del evento porque a lo
maybe I could find her because she was
mejor te la encontraba porque estaba
nominated and didn't go and didn't go and didn't cry and
nominada y no fue y no fue y no lloró y
then I had it here prepared just in
entonces lo tenía yo aquí preparado por
case to put people in
si acaso para poner a la gente en
context do you remember what day It would be more or
contexto te acuerdas qué día Sería más o
less it's been a while but well
menos es que ha pasado tiempo pero bueno
speak today well more Valente better
habla hoy pues más Valente más vale
late than never in my life but I don't know I
tarde que nunca en mi vida pero no sé yo
think two little sisters have passed not around
creo que han pasado dos hermanitas no
there  see we're not going to look
por ahí a ver tampoco vamos a buscar
among all of Soraya's tweets let's see on
entre todos los tweets de Soraya a ver
November 26th but not the same no less
el 26 de noviembre pero tanto no menos
no the same yeah eh watch out Well a month I don't
no igual sí eh ojito Bueno un mes no
think so no I don't
creo no
know why they invented the
no sé por qué se han inventado ahora la
word trinker now when for all their life
palabra trinker cuando de todo la vida
if they deleted it it's not here unless they've
si la borraba por aquí no está a no ser
deleted it someone can
lo ha borrado alguien nos puede
confirm if they've deleted it it was like I don't know
confirmar si lo ha borrado era como no
why the word trincher is used now
sé por qué ahora se utiliza la palabra
when they've always been
trincher cuando de toda la vida se les
called I don't know if it was [ __ ] Or
ha llamado No sé si era [__] O
what the word was but something
cuál era la palabra que pero algo así
like imbeciles or something like that
como imbéciles o algo así
[ __ ] I would love to see I would
[__] es que me encantaría ver Me
love to see the tweet or hasn't
encantaría ver el tweet o no lo tiene
anyone captured it or has anyone uploaded it captured
nadie capturado o nadie subido capturado
Yeah because we go on YouTube that
Sí porque nos metemos en YouTube a que
people say they deleted it I think they
lo ha borrado dice la gente creo que sí
deleted it I think they deleted it they deleted it the
lo borró creo lo ha borrado lo borró al
next day and nobody has it man if it
día siguiente y nadie lo tiene hombre si
was a clear it's because Jolie I don't have it
fue un claro es que Jolie no lo tengo
Yeah because the media No not even I
Sí porque los medios No ni yo me hice
echoed That's
Eco De eso
the fashion of calling trinkers and things like that to
la moda de llamar trinkers y cosas así a
those who are lifelong imbeciles
los que son unos imbéciles de toda la
What a desire to camouflage what  It's with
vida Qué ganas de camuflar lo que es con
how beautiful it is to call things by
lo bonito que es Llamar a las cosas por
their proper name it's like super gratuitous
su propio nombre es como súper gratuito
or whatever But why so but was it
o sea Pero por qué tan pero esta fue
really her because in this capture it doesn't
ella de verdad porque en esta captura no
appear No it wasn't her In fact I spoke
sale No no fue ella De hecho yo hablé
with her at the time with one of her
con su momento con uno de sus
representatives and he said It's that she always gets into
representantes y dijo Es que siempre se
trouble she says look what I'm telling her
mete el líos dice mira que se lo digo
but but yes she put this and then she put something else she
pero pero sí puso esto y luego puso otra
answered no more I mean There's more
cosa contestó no a más O sea Hay más
after that I think let's
después de eso creo
see I think so eh or if not maybe they haven't
a ver creo que sí eh o si no igual no lo
put it there here it doesn't appear anymore it's
han puesto ahí aquí ya no sale es que
okay it was her answering answering or I mean I
vale fue ella contestando contestando o
remember perfectly that she
sea lo recuerdo perfectamente que
answered how is it that I don't know Something
contestaba como es que no lo sé Algo
similar to that but it wasn't that I do
similar a eso pero no era eso
n't know here it does appear verified in the
No lo sé aquí sí sale verificado en el
video of our friend Lucía if you think
vídeo de nuestra amiga Lucía si piensas
something I'll let you know oh oh we talked about calling
algo te lo voy ay ay hablamos de llamar
okay
vale
here of course it's not there but let's say that it's
aquí desde luego no está pero vamos que
free no I mean like you can
que gratuito no O sea en plan puedes
send your support to Rocío Carrasco without
mandarle tu apoyo a Rocío Carrasco sin
without saying this no I mean if they are not
sin decir esto no O sea si a ti no te
attacking you and you have nothing to
están atacando y tú no tienes nada que
do with the move this This is the other thing
ver con la movida esto Esto es lo otro
no This is the other thing it's the same the same it
no Esto es lo otro es el mismo el mismo
's  the same but it says Show
es el mismo pero es que pone Mostrar
thread there was no I don't understand
hilo no había no entiendo
Oh sure it
Ah claro
's true it says so but no it doesn't say it they don't
es verdad lo pone pero no no lo pone no
put it in the video it doesn't say it Lucía
lo ponen en el vídeo no lo pone Lucía
Lucía we send a huge kiss queen if
Lucía mandamos un beso enorme reina si
you're watching us this other friend from YouTube that I don't know that isn't an account someone has messed with her about the blue tide or people who support Antonio Navío or something like that or Antonio Vila has done something to her know no well we have Soraya's explanation you have spoken with
explicación de Soraya tú has hablado con
Soraya today by phone
Soraya hoy por teléfono
today Okay but no but she left me this topic
hoy Bueno pero no pero este tema me lo
in a message we have spoken by
ha dejado en mensaje hemos hablado por
audios but this But also how nice it
audios pero este Pero además que maja ha
was that she left me this specific explanation
sido que esta explicación concreta me lo
in a message that I'm going to
ha dejado en un mensaje que yo voy a
read literally
leer literalmente
Dino Dino let's see
Dino Dino a ver
Soraya after almost three weeks of
Soraya después de casi tres semanas de
this moment that made her stay
este momento que que le hizo quedarse
calvanelas says the following I
calvanelas dice lo siguiente
don't know much about this matter of Rocío and Antonio David Ah perfect I do
David no sé mucho Ah perfecto
n't usually get involved in anyone's business it has
No suelo meterme en asuntos de nadie
become very clear
ha quedado muy claro
the truth is that I thought that
la verdad es que pensaba que eso de
trinker was something else I
trinker era otra cosa
never associated it with this matter then I
jamás lo asocié a este asunto luego me
found out what it was but of course as I don't
enteré de lo que era pero claro como no
know  none of that story
sé nada de esa historia
ratchet in German is drunk
trinquete en alemán es borracho
to another there's more there's more but come on it
a otro hay más hay más pero vamos que
went in one ear and out the other they do
por un oído me entró y por otro me salió
n't affect me in the slightest
ni me afectan lo más mínimo estas
I work with Rocio on the Friday program I do
Yo trabajo con Rocío en el programa de
n't know which one it is and she's very affectionate and very
no sé cuál es y es muy cariñosa y muy
polite I can't say anything bad about her the
educada no puedo decir nada malo de ella
end to another dog with that collar eh to
fin a otro perro con ese collar eh a
another dog with that collar and now they're going to
otro perro con ese collar y ahora van a
say Dog doesn't eat dog listen to me no it doesn't
decir Perro no come perro escúchame no
work let's see point number one What is it what is
no cuela a ver punto número uno Cuál es
the program that he
el cuál es el programa con el que
works with Rocio Carrasco on
trabaja con Rocío Carrasco de los
Fridays but I don't know if
viernes pero yo que sé si no me lo sabe
she can't tell me on the mediafés Night fever on
decir ella en el mediafés Night fever de
Fridays You work there Soraya Yes yes she's on the
los viernes Ahí trabajas Soraya Sí sí
jury she's on the jury of course let's
está de Jurado está de Jurado claro a
see of course if you're working in the
ver claro si estás trabajando en la
TV factory with Rocio Carrasco it's
fábrica de la tele con Rocío Carrasco es
because because you're eager
porque porque estás deseando
obviously of course So it's a
evidentemente claro Entonces es un
program totally unrelated to her history
programa totalmente ajeno a su historia
really But well of course I suppose that of
en verdad Pero bueno claro Supongo que
course
claro
the songs even the songs like
las canciones hasta las canciones como
pulling a barb don't you remember when they
tirando pulla no te acuerdas cuando le
gave Ana Maria the gift as if a
pusieron a Ana María el don como si una
song were indirect of
canción fuera indirecta de
Ortega Cano or part of here No, of course, and
Ortega Cano o parte de acá No claro y
Alba with Jorge Pérez and of course, of course, they
Alba con Jorge Pérez y claro claro no
are not stupid, it is the subject, I mean, look,
son bobos yo es el tema o sea mira que
we should make the subject but they do
nosotros que hagamos el tema pero ellos
not let go of the single subject either, eh, I
el monotema no lo sueltan tampoco eh o
mean, they already have it like Seville as
sea ellos ya lo tienen como Sevilla como
something personal You know, but I do not believe
algo a lo personal Sabes pero no me creo
at all, family, what you think, I do
para nada familia que piensen ustedes yo
not believe at all what she told you I
no me creo para nada lo que te ha dicho
mean, she told you for the people, it
O sea ella te lo ha dicho para la gente
seems that she is joining,
es que veo que se está incorporando
I seem to be the moderator here too, I
parezco Yo también la moderadora de aquí
see that more
que veo que se está incorporando más
people are joining and if it seems to you, I will read it again
gente y si te parece lo vuelvo a leer
in case someone has not
por si acaso alguien no le ha quedado
understood it, it seems fine to me, come on, but with
claro me parece bien venga pero con
intensity, eh As if it were that matter
intensidad eh Como si fuera ese asunto
Read it as if you were her telling us,
Léelo como si fueras ella diciéndonoslo
as if we had an audio of her
como si tuviéramos un audio de ella
saying this to an audio of her, okay, I
diciendo esto a un audio de ella vale
don't know much about that matter of Rocío and Antonio David, the truth is, I do not usually
David no sé mucho la verdad No suelo
get involved in anyone's business, the truth is
meterme en asuntos de nadie la verdad es
that I thought that this trinque thing was
que pensaba que eso de trinque era otra
something else, I never associate it with that matter, then I
cosa jamás lo asocia ese asunto luego me
found out what it was but of course, since I know
enteré de que era pero claro como no sé
nothing  from that story
nada de esa historia
trinker in German means drunk
trinker en alemán es borracho
but let's say it went in one ear and out the
pero vamos que por un oído me entró y
other it doesn't affect me in the
por otro me salió ni me afecta lo más
slightest these wars I work with
mínimo estas guerras Yo trabajo con
Rocio on the Friday show
Rocío en el programa de los viernes
and she's very affectionate and polite I can't
y es muy cariñosa y educada no puedo
say anything bad about her because of her I live
decir nada malo de ella por ella Vivo
for her what a goal
por ella que meta
give your opinion while about this now
di tu opinión de mientras de esto ahora
I'll give you mine
te doy yo la mía
man
hombre
well my opinion on this let's see I
pues mi opinión de esto a ver yo es que
have esteem for Soraya
a Soraya la tengo
from the interviews and such and she has
estima de las entrevistas y tal y
always been very generous and very nice
siempre ha sido muy generosa y muy maja
yes it's true that Soraya is a girl
sí que es verdad que Soraya es una tía
who has always been involved in
que siempre ha estado envuelta en
controversy because she has always said whatever she wants so
polémica porque siempre ha dicho lo que
sometimes saying whatever she wants I
le da la gana entonces a veces decir lo
want some
que le da la gana Quiero unas
consequences and if not let them not tell
consecuencias y si no que no lo digan a
us because here we are bald
nosotros que aquí estamos calvos ya
after a year and a half But well I
después de un año y medio Pero bueno
think that in this case I
creo que en este caso
don't know to what extent it's true and I would
o sea no sé hasta qué punto de verdad y
say the opposite eh but in this case I don't know
diría lo contrario eh pero este no sé
to what extent she has been aware
hasta qué punto ha sido consciente
because I don't know to what extent it compensates her to
porque no sé hasta qué punto le compensa
put the word trinque as if
el poner la palabra trinque como
doing I mean it's not She is a girl that I
haciendo O sea no es Ella es una tía que
understand that if you have to row to  favor
yo entiendo que si hay que remar a favor
on one side she will do it but from there to
de un lado lo va a hacer pero de ahí a
absolutely destroy a sector
cargarse absolutamente a un sector no
music is not very good today and even
está la música hoy muy bien hoy en día y
less in her case to destroy
menos en su caso como para cargarse a
thousands of blues I want to tell you that it is not
miles azules te quiero decir que no es
very it is not a very
muy no es una estrategia demasiado
intelligent strategy because it has been very shameless
inteligente porque ha sido muy descarado
So I Soraya from here I am going to
Entonces yo Soraya desde aquí le voy a
give her a vote of confidence and in fact
dar un voto de confianza y de hecho
I was thinking of calling her and making a joke on
pensaba llamarla y hacerle la broma a
her but I have not dared maybe for
ella pero no me he atrevido igual para
the next one Javier how do you see it
la próxima Javier cómo lo ves
yes yes yes yes yes yes
sí sí sí sí sí sí sí
the truth is that she is not always
la verdad es que ella no no siempre es
good really the photocolos I
buena de verdad los photocolos me
remember the pride that came with her
acuerdo en el orgullo que vino con su
daughter who came or rather always good I think she
hija que vino o sea siempre buena creo
is a special aunt let's remember in the
que es una tía especial recordemos en
pandemic she went out into the street inside her
pandemia salió a la calle dentro de su
mansion and stood next to a tree and
casoplón y se puso al lado de un árbol y
started to cry because
se puso a llorar porque se le había
a tree had died and she broadcast it on
muerto un árbol y lo retransmitió en
Instagram Let's see it is special but the
instagram A ver es especial pero el
fuchsia tide tree might be why she was
árbol de la marea fucsia igual
crying I
por eso lloraba
can't get over all this that you are
no puedo superar todo esto que me estás
telling me Javi It's that life if it is really
diciendo Javi Es que la vida si de
clearer than what you have said it is worth
más claro de lo que tú lo has dicho vale
a Bible Of course you in case you  you
por una Biblia Claro que tú por si tú
are little Clara okay
eres poco Clara vale
here for me what has happened more than
aquí para mí lo que ha pasado más que
evidently is what is called a
evidentemente es lo que se llama una
total cable collection has gone
recogida de cables total se ha venido
overboard because she is working with the
arriba porque está trabajando con la
TV factory and she said I am going to
fábrica de la tele y ha dicho me voy a
earn some points here with the bosses
ganar aquí unos puntillos con los jefes
and she said to the led teachers what
y ha dicho a los maestros llevados qué
is happening that the teacher Joao the
es lo que pasa que el maestro Joao el
led teacher his profession is to say
maestro llevado su profesión es decir
that he predicts the future in a
que adivina el futuro en una bola de
crystal ball then that business was more
cristal entonces ese negocio era más
damaged it cannot be damaged but
perjudicado no se puede perjudicar pero
she works in the world of music and there
ella trabaja en el mundo de la música y
is always an unwritten rule in the
siempre hay una norma no escrita en el
world of music and that is that she does not get involved
mundo de la música y es que no se meta
in positioning in divisions in a
en posicionamiento en divisiones en plan
total political plan So when she wanted to
total Entonces cuando se ha querido
win The medal with The bosses on one
ganar La medallita con Los jefes por un
side but on the other side the Replay
lado pero por el otro lado el Replay le
will have told her
habrá dicho
listen to me What are you doing like do not
escúchame Qué estás haciendo en plan no
throw people from like that
te eches a lo alto a gente de o sea
because here here there can easily
porque aquí aquí tranquilamente puede
be
haber
70% of trencher who listen to your
un 70% de trincher que escuchan tu
music and 30% of fuchsia If you are going to
música y un 30% de fucsia Si te vas a
lock yourself in staying only with the
encerrar en quedarte solamente con los
fuchsia you are going to run out of listeners anyway
fucsia te vas a quedar sin oyentes igual
but look Javi  I don't know if Soraya's is weaker
pero fíjate Javi No sé si es más débil
or if we have
lo de Soraya o que llevemos
1427 likes minutes away from hitting the jackpot,
1427 likes a minutos de dar el bombazo
at least 2000 please no, she
mínimo 2000 por favor que no que de
really deserves it, she even
verdad que lo merece si es que hasta se
falls, very poor, she even falls,
cae muy pobre si es que hasta se cae
my goodness
madre mía
[Music]
[Música]